One Magic Christmas is a family, fantasy film directed by Phillip Borsos.
Ginny Grainger, a young mother, rediscovers the joy and beauty of Christmas, thanks to the unshakable
faith of her six-year-old daughter Abbie and Gideon, Ginny's very own guardian angel.
Ginny Grainger, played by Mary Steenburgen.
Jack Grainger, played by Gary Basaraba.
Abbie Grainger, played by Elisabeth Harnois.
Caleb Grainger, played by Arthur Hill.
Harry Dickens, played by Wayne Robson.
Santa Claus, played by Jan Rubeš.
One Magic Christmas is a 1985 Christmas fantasy film directed by Phillip Borsos.
It was released by Walt Disney Pictures and stars Mary
Steenburgen and Harry Dean Stanton.
It was shot in Meaford, Ontario with some scenes in Owen Sound, Ontario, Canada.
The film explores themes of parent child relationship, holiday, christmas.